Guide to the Elizabeth S. Lyman Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional papers, Accession ARCH-2000-074
  - ALF/N Board Meeting 5/18/1996 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - ALF/N Board Meeting 2/29-3/3/1996 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - ALF/N CLIA Coordinator 1997 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - ALF/N Trip 11/22-27/1995 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - ALF/N CLIA Wells Fargo 1997 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - ALF/N CLIA Fundraising (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - ALF/N CLIA Surdna 1997 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - ALF/N CLIA Time 1997 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - ALF/N General (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - ALF/N Roundtable 6/1996 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - ALF/N Trip 8/11-12/1996 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - ALF/N Miscellaneous 1996 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - ALF/N Board Meeting 5/20-23/1999 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - ALF/N Team packet (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - ALF/N CLIA Trip 10/26-30/1997 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - ALF/N Board Meeting 5/14-17/1998 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Memoranda (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - NCWE Banking (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - NCWE Dissolution Papers 1992 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - NCWE Dissolution 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - NCWE HUB Articles of Incorporation, By Laws (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - NCWE Closing Mailing 1989 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - NCWE Financial Statement 1989 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - NCWE New York Department of Tax & Finance 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - HUB Surveys (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - HUB/Enterprise (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - HUB Rosemary Young Luncheon 6/1990 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - HUB Rolodex (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Publications 1994-1996 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Europe Background (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - ALF/N (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - GSB Conference on Entrepreneurship 1998 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - John Gardner Fellowship 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - YWCA Conference 1998 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - National IDA Learning Conference 1998 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Trip 1/17-20/1999 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Center for Policy Alternatives packet (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Y2K 1998 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - IDA Trip 3/23-26/1998 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Putnam School 1997 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - AEO 1998 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Council on Foundations/ALF "Grantmaking for the Global Village" (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - ALF/Silicon Valley Involve! (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Publications 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - AEO Organizing Event 6/20-22/1991 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - AEO Gathering of Different Voices (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - AEO Celebration (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - AEO Reimbursement (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - AEO Evaluation Sheets 6/1991 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - AEO Structure & Membership Committee (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - AEO Recommendations (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - AEO Conference planning (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - AEO General 1991 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - AEO Participant & Registration Lists (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - AEO Mailed Packets (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - AEO Committee & Workshop Reports (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - AEO Trip 2/26-27/1991 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - HUB Local Site Information for NCWE 1989 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - HUB Boston (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - HUB D.C.- Capitol Area NCWE (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - HUB Chicago 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - HUB Dallas 1983 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - HUB Flint, Michigan 1987 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - HUB Greenville, Mississippi 1987 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - HUB Minnesota/St. Paul 1983 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - HUB Newark 1984 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - HUB New York City 1990 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - HUB New York State Division on Women (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - HUB North Carolina 1989 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - HUB Philadelphia 1989 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - HUB Pittsburgh NCWE (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - HUB San Francisco Bay Area (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - HUB Seattle (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - HUB Stamford (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - HUB D.C. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - HUB NCWE Hartford (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - HUB New Haven 1989 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - HUB New London (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - HUB Site Development General (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - HUB Temple University 1994 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Memoranda 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Enterprise Foundation Conference 10/14/1994 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Duggan Christmas 1994 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Enterprise Foundation Trip 1/6/1995 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Banducci 1/1995 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - IRWG 1995 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board bios 1995 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 7/13/1995 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Enterprise Foundation Financial Review & Audit Committee Meeting 7/1995 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Enterprise Foundation Leadership America Trip 7/8/1995 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Enterprise Foundation East Palo Alto Plugged In packet (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Enterprise Foundation Strategic Plan 1995-2000 7/13/1995 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 4/27/1995 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Enterprise Foundation Financial Review & Audit Committee 4/1995 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Enterprise Foundation Greater Miami Neighborhood packet (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 2/2/1995 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Long Range Planning Committee Meeting 1/5/1994 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 2/2/1995 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Enterprise Foundation 1995 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Enterprise Foundation Strategic Plan Draft 5/25/1991 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Enterprise Foundation General 1992-1994 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Aspen Directory of Microenterprise Programs 1994 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Individual Development Accounts Conference 8/1995 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - AEO 1995 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Women's Wire (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Memoranda 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous Publications 1995 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Women's Economic Agenda Project 1987 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Women's Bureau packet (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Women in Non-Traditional Employment packet (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Urgent Action 1998 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - UNIFEM (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Technoserve (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - 20% by 2020 1994 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Students for Responsible Business 1998 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Stevenson House (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Stanford University Women's Field Hockey Endowment (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Small Business Administration 1989-1991 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Shatter It! (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Responsible Wealth packet (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Resourceful Women packet (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - National Women's Business Council 1990 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - National Women's Health Network (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - New Ways to Work (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - National Training & Information Center (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - National Retiree Volunteer Coalition (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - National Network on Women as Philanthropists (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - National Museum of Women in the Arts 1993 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - National Low Income Housing Coalition (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - National Conference of Christians & Jews 1992 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Mosaic Health (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Mills Women & Leadership (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Low Income Housing Information Services (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Local Initiatives Support 1992 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Liberty Bidco Investment Co. (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - The Leadership Group, Inc. (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Kaiser Washington Post Harvard Survey (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Institute for Women's Policy Research (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Independent Sector 1994 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - InfoActive (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Girl Scouts (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Experience Corporation (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Earth Circle Foundation (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Equity Institute 1994 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Drucker Foundation (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - National Council for Economic Development (CUED) (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Creative Associates (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Eulau Institute 1994 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Clearinghouse for Mid-Continental Foundations (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - City Innovation (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Center for Ecology & Social Justice 1992 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Center for American Women & Politics (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - California Tomorrow (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Business Enterprise Trust (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Balancing Works (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - American Women's Economic Development Corp Newsletters 1988-1994 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Ashoka (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Arthri-Sea Coastal Bioresources (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Amigos de los Americas (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Amnesty International 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - AEO Trip 5/18-21/1994 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - AEO Meeting 5/18-21/1994 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - AEO Directories 1991, 1992, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - AEO SBA Microloan RFP 1993 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - O'Regan/Conway Microenterprise Report 1993 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Aspen Directory of U.S. Microenterprise Programs 1994, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Publications (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - IDA 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Inquiries 1993 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Trip- Columbus 5/17-20/1995 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Resource Organizations (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Publications 1993-1995 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Exchange (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Gender Analysis Papers 1992 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Birch, David (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Brush, Candida (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Francisco, Victoria (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Mayer, Michael (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Novocratz, Jacqueline 1994 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Nye, Nancy (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Local Women in Business (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Accion 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Aspen Institute 1992 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Coastal Enterprises, Inc. (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Community Capital Bank (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - First Nations Development Institute (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Institute for Community Economics (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - WBDC Maine (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Microcredit Summit 1998 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Office of Refugee Resettlement 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Philadelphia WERC (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Working Capital (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - American Institute of Small Business (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Corporation for Enterprise Development 1987-1994 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Eastside Community Investments (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - GROW (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Marketplace (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Neighborhood Reinvestment (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Prism Venture Partners (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Women's Self-Employment Project 1990-1998 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - AISEP (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - CAMEO (California Association for Microenterprise Opportunity) Meeting 5/4/1995 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - CAMEO 1995-1997 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - CAMEO Trip 5/3-4/1995 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Welfare to Work 2/18-20/1999 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - FIELD Microenterprise Fund packet 1998 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Involve! 1996 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Homeless in Olympia Report (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Notes (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Trip - Virginia 4/24-27/1996 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - National Immigration Forum 1996 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - John Gardner Fellows 1996 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - American Institutes for Research packet 1996 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Alliance for National Renewal 6/7/1996 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - AEO Meeting 5/4/1996 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - AEO 5/1-4/1996 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Enterprise Foundation Trip 4/30/1996 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Enterprise Foundation packet 1997 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Publications (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Rosenberg Foundation 1998 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - YWCA 1996 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Foundation Center Trip 11/16 - 12/3/1996 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 11/12/1998 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Enterprise Foundation Executive Committee & Financial Review & Audit Committee Combined Meeting 11/1998 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Enterprise Foundation Trip 12/3-7/1998 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Network Philadelphia Regional Directory (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous Articles re: Affirmative Action, Leadership, Microenterprise, Philanthropy, Welfare, Women 1991-1995 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Files on Persons: Allee-Yates 1983-1995 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Sandtown-Winchester Draft Proposal 1993 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Working Assets Board Reports 5-7/1994 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Working Assets Board Meeting 5/16/1994 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Working Assets Board Meeting 8/8/1994 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Unemployment Insurance- U.S. Dept. of Labor Reports (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Fannie Mae Maxwell Awards 1994 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Minority/Women's Business packet (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Enterprise Foundation Financial Review & Audit Committee Meeting 7/1994 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Enterprise Foundation Financial Review & Audit Committee Meeting 10/1993 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Enterprise Foundation (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Enterprise Foundation Conference 12/2-4/1993 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Enterprise Foundation Financial Statements 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Enterprise Foundation Financial Review & Audit Committee Meeting 11/1994 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 11/16/1994 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Enterprise Foundation Shelter Network of San Mateo County (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Enterprise Foundation Communities for Change (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Enterprise Foundation Hope From Homes (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Enterprise Foundation Financial Review & Audit Committee Meeting 4/1994 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 4/14/1999 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Enterprise Foundation Long Range Planning Committee 9/23/1994 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 7/14/1994 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Enterprise Foundation Conference 10/13-15/1994 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - ALF/Silicon Valley Board Retreat 2/8/1997 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - ALF/Silicon Valley 1997 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - ALF/Silicon Valley Senior Fellows (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - ALF/Silicon Valley Board 5/16/1996 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - ALF/Silicon Valley Financial Statements 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - ALF/Silicon Valley Board 5/16/1996 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - ALF/Silicon Valley Board Retreat 2/3/1996 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - ALF/Silicon Valley 1995 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - ALF/Silicon Valley Board Retreat 10/6-7/1995 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - ALF/Silicon Valley Board 5/17/1995 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - ALF/Silicon Valley Board Retreat 2/11/1995 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - ALF/Silicon Valley 1994 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - ALF/Silicon Valley Computer Network Task Force (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - ALF/Silicon Valley Kendall Speech 1991 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Leadership California Advisory Committee 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Leadership California packet 1994 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Current Events Club 1995 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - United Way Strategic Plan 1990 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Independent Sector Give Five packet 1990 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Valentino, Christina (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - AARP Women's Initiative (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - IBM 1992 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Kellogg Foundation - Adams 1991 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Boorn, Mary Lynne 1988 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - John Gardner Fellow- Buckman 1990 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - April Trust (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Gilbert, April (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Shaevitz, Geoff (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - NC Equity (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Young, Grace (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Priority One (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Richmond, Virginia (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Meclenburg, Paul (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Massarsky, Cynthia (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Long, Marcelle (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Duffy, Liz (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Carter, Kimberly (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Bethel, Karen (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Bekooy, Elizabeth (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Barr, Joan (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Baker, Gwen (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Women Work! (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - ALF/Silicon Valley 1993 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Global Fund for Women 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Ms. Foundation (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - IRWG Newsletters 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Women & Foundations/Corporate Philanthropy 1985 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Bethune Museum (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Company of Women 1991 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Families in Transition 1989 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Future Education Films (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Child Care Law Center (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Information Please (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Jurismonitor (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Kellogg Foundation (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Meta Network (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Nation's Labor (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Nannycare (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Women Inventors Project (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Women's Leadership Network 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Institute for Women's Leadership (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - San Jose Development Corp. 1989 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - SF WISE (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - HUB Hartford/Newark Project Design Meeting 1/9/1986 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - AEO San Jose Catholic Charities (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Grand Rapids 1992 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Michigan Strategic Fund 1990 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - NCWE Palo Alto (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Social Development Council Ontario CN (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - NCWE Los Angeles (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - HUB Los Angeles 1989 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - HUB Oakland (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - HUB D.C. (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - 100 Women East Palo Alto (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Council for Community –Based Development 1988 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Enterprise Foundation/NCWE Handbook 1989 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Human Services Management Institute (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - HUB, Perth Surveys (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - California Legislative Task Force 1987 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - California Legislative Task Force 1988 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - AEO Trip 6/18-20/1992 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - AEO Newsletter (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - AEO 1993 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - AEO Rural Enterprise Assistance Fund (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - AEO Nevada Self-Employment Trust (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - AEO Nevada Women's Fund (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - YWCA (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - WISE 1991 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - AEO Jubilee West (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Lenders for Community Development (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Northern California Community Loan Fund (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - CWED (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - East Palo Alto (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - CAMEO 1994 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Working Assets Board, Audit Committee Meetings 11/12/1990 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Working Assets Trip 8/8-11/1992 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Working Assets Board, Audit Committee Meetings 8/5/1991 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Working Assets Fiske Report 1991 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Working Assets General 1991 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Working Assets Board Meeting 11/9/1992 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Working Assets Board, Audit Committee Meetings (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Working Assets Board Meeting 5/18/1992 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Working Assets 1992 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Working Assets Board Meeting 3/11-12/1992 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Working Assets Board, Audit Committee Meetings 11/11/1991 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Working Assets 1991 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Enterprise Senior Ventures Directors Meeting 5/1/1998 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Enterprise Senior Ventures 1998-2000 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Enterprise Senior Ventures 1997 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Women of Stanford University Advisor (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Academy of Leadership packet (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Academy of Leadership 11/6-7/1998 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - ALF/Silicon Valley Corporate Community Involvement Study (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Clever, Linda (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Christmas in April 1998 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - AEO Policy (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Current Events Club 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Current Events Club 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Current Events Club 1989-1991 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Enterprise Foundation 1998 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Environmental Careers Organization (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Foundation Center (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Global Fund for Women 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Institute for Current World Affairs (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - IRWG President's Council (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - IRWG 1997-1999 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Leadership America Trip 3/11/-15/1995 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Leadership California 1998 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Mid-Peninsula Citizens for Fair Housing (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Ms. Foundation (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Calendars 1994, 1995, 1996, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - California Legislature Certificate of Recognition for Jing Lyman 5/31/1998 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Publications 1998 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - ALF 1998 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Leadership California Program Planning 1996 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Putney School 1995 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Women Innovators 1995 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - UNDP 1991 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Rural Development Leadership Network 1991-1992 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Scribbling Women 1994 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Select Committee on Hunger 1991 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Professional Women in Construction (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Rainforest Indian Museum (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Pratt Institute PICCED (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - NCRW 1992-1997 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - National Network of Hispanic Women 1988 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Michigan Women's Foundation (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Private Agencies Collaborating Together (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Older Women's League 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Putney School 1996 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - WEP/YWCA/Catholic Charities Wages Proposals (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1982-1988 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Independent Sector/John Gardner Fellowship 1987 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous Publications (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Jing Lyman X-rays 1987 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Mensendieck Books, Signed 1984 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Barred Island 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Schauffler 1979-1983 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Manchester 1980 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - ALF/Silicon Valley Board 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - ALF/Silicon Valley 1990-1992 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - ALF/Silicon Valley Exec. Committee 1991 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - ALF/N Drafts (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - ALF/N "Take Me on a Journey" 1997 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - ALF/N Program 10/1991 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - ALF/N Administration 1991 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - ALF/N Board (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - ALF/N Executive Committee (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - ALF/N Strategic Planning (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - ALF/N Trip 5/1-4/1991 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - ALF/N Finance (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - ALF/N Research (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - ALF/N Directors Meeting 11/20-22/1991 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - ALF/N Strategic Development Plan 1992 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - ALF/N "Effecting Community Change" (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - ALF/N Stanford University (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - ALF/N General (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - ALF/N Job Applicants (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - ALF/N Administrative Memoranda (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - ALF/N Correspondence (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - ALF/N Strategic Plan (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - ALF/N Board 1/31/1992 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - ALF/N Financial Statements 1990 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - ALF/N Board Dinners 1/30-31/1992 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - ALF/N Board Meeting 5/29-31/1992 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - ALF/N Board Meeting 11/6-7/1992 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - ALF/N Board Conference call 11/5/1993 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - ALF/N Leadership Readings 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - ALF/N Board Conference call 11/2/1994 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - ALF/N Board Meeting 4/27-30/1995 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - ALF/N Board Meeting 4/28-5/1/1994 (Box 25, Folder 6)